Make a killing. Make a living.
The Sisters Brothers is a western, drama, comedy
film directed by Jacques Audiard.
Oregon, 1851.
Hermann Kermit Warm, a chemist and aspiring gold prospector, keeps a profitable secret that the Commodore wants to
know, so he sends the Sisters brothers, two notorious assassins, to capture him on his way to California.
Eli Sisters, played by John C. Reilly.
Charlie Sisters, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
John Morris, played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Hermann Kermit Warm, played by Riz Ahmed.
Mayfield, played by Rebecca Root.
Girl Mayfield Saloon, played by Allison Tolman.
The Sisters Brothers is a 2018 Western film directed by Jacques Audiard from a screenplay he
co-wrote with Thomas Bidegain, based on the novel of the same name by Patrick deWitt.
An American and French co-production, it is
Audiard's first English-language work.
The film stars John C.
Reilly (who also produced) and Joaquin Phoenix as the notorious assassin brothers Eli and Charlie Sisters, and follows the two
brothers as they chase after two men (Jake Gyllenhaal and Riz Ahmed) who have banded together to search for gold.
The film had its world premiere at the Venice International Film Festival on 2 September 2018, where it won the
Silver Lion for Best Direction, and was theatrically released in the United States on 21 September 2018.
The Sisters Brothers received positive reviews from critics, with most praise
going to its performances, characters, direction and soundtrack.
It was a box office bomb, grossing $14.1 million
against its $38 million production budget.
It was the final feature film featuring Rutger Hauer released before his death,
although he had finished filming several projects released after his death.
The film explores themes of gold, based on novel or book,
hitman, san francisco, california, male friendship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.